Let's kick it up a notch, Itadori!
This will be the last time
you and I curse each other!
Hey, now.
Are you leaving me out?
He severed it himself?!
Soul Multiplicity.
By combining souls with weak
rejection, it creates an amalgamation.
Polymorphic Soul Isomer!
What is that transfigured human?!
Given that he's able to
hold off me and my brother,
the distribution of power
between his bodies is likely 2 to 8.
And the weakened 2 is the main body!
I'll make certain my brother crushes it!
I've heard its transfigured humans
are around grade 3 or a weak grade 2!
Crush it quickly, Aoi Todo!
What?!
Todo!
That's for underestimating me!
It's dead?
It had so much power,
yet it only took a single blow?
Now I see!
It managed to gain explosive power by
burning through multiple souls in an instant!
It's an extremely offense-oriented
transfigured human.
And...
there are two more?
Forgive me, you pitiful souls.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
I've finished getting us away
from the topknot gorilla.
Now to just
take him down!
Tsk.
It would seem you're dead
set on leaving me out, huh?
I guess I couldn't completely take him down
with two Polymorphic Soul Isomers.
Landing any blow on this guy
is a rather steep hurdle.
But if I unleash my domain,
I'll touch Sukuna and get killed.
Barriers are complex.
I already revealed the option
of excluding him from my domain.
The same ploy won't work on Itadori again.
So what do I do, then?
The one who taught me that was...
Domain Expansion:
Self-Embodiment of Perfection!
I thought that was suicide for it?!
It's a desperate gamble!
On a 0.2-second domain expansion!
Todo moved to protect himself
from the domain,
activating the Simple Domain he
learned directly from Yuki Tsukumo.
Itadori acted even faster,
racing forth to exorcise Mahito
before he unleashed Idle Transfiguration.
Though Mahito activated his
technique even faster than that.
The manifestation of an innate domain
is usually followed by
the activation of a technique,
but he merged those two
separate steps into one.
It was an act of speed made possible by his
awakened state that followed Black Flash.
I take it I'm safe this time, Sukuna?
Knowing you, you have some kind of
backup plan with Itadori, right?
I won't let you, though.
I'll kill Itadori before
you switch with him.
So shut up and watch from here.
Todo!
Come on, I just made you more fashionable.
After deploying a domain,
the technique engraved into the body
is temporarily burned out,
and using it proves challenging.
Mahito already understood that after
his flight from Satozakura High School.
Black Flash!
He just...
focused all his damn cursed
energy in his stomach on instinct!
However, my technique has recovered!
And he can't clap his hands anymore!
This time, I'll kill him for certain!
Huh?
Takada-chan - "Climax☆JUMPING!"
*Todo's imagination
Shit!
Black Flash!
Hmph!
It was just for a moment, but I touched him.
It's a miracle I got off with only this.
Leave the rest to me, Todo!
Thank you, Todo!
Damn it!
I can't believe I took another
Black Flash dead-on at that moment!
That damn gorilla screwed
with me until the very end.
But now I've finally grasped it.
The true essence of my soul! Its true shape!
Idle Transfiguration...
Instant Spirit Body of Distorted Killing!
It's a happy birthday,
Itadori!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
This isn't a transformation
as just a means, like before.
What's different?
I understood after using Black Flash.
What my true, unbridled soul is.
I'm shocked.
You didn't strike me as the type
to go on a journey of self-discovery.
That's true.
But I'm just starting on the final touches.
After I kill you, I'll finally
be truly born into this world.
So tough!
Its bare body
is even harder than his was!
I understood after using Black Flash.
What my true, unbridled soul is.
Is that what he meant?!
This thing has already...
become something on a different level
than the cursed spirit he was
prior to transforming?!
If I want to defeat this thing,
I'll have to hit him with a Black Flash
There is no sorcerer who can unleash a Black Flash at will
using my maximum cursed energy!
Even if I only used it for
a moment, getting hit with
a Black Flash right after my
domain expansion was real bad.
We're both
still brimming with energy, huh?!
There is no one who can unleash
a Black Flash at will.
But something about him convinces
me that the current Itadori can.
In which case...
A time lag?!
Hey, cursed spirit.
There's no way you don't understand this.
Arms are just decorations.
The act of applause
is an acclamation of the soul!
I haven't switched places?!
It's unfortunate.
My Boogie Woogie is already dead.
Black Flash!
Not yet!
My stock of transfigured humans is also out!
I'll accept it, Mahito.
I am you.
I wanted to reject you.
I wanted to pretend I didn't
understand what you said.
But that's different now.
I'll just kill you.
And if you're ever reborn again as
a new curse, I'll kill you then, too.
You can change your name
and change your appearance,
but I'll still kill you again and again.
I don't need meaning or
a reason for it anymore.
Maybe there will be
some meaning to be found
from my actions several
centuries after I'm dead.
But I'm sure I'm just...
one big cog in the wheel.
And I'll keep on killing curses
until I rust away.
Because that is my role in this war.
Geto!
Shall I save you, Mahito?
Episode 45
Metamorphosis
A contrived fate may not be true destiny.
But the moment such fake destinies
intertwine will nonetheless be true destiny.
Next time, "Metamorphosis, Part 2."
Next Episode
Metamorphosis, Part 2
Some things can only be cultivated under pretenses.